MemWal plus plus — hybrid verifiable memory for autonomous agents. Built for Sui Overflow and the Walrus track. Local speed, Walrus truth, on-chain economy.
MemWal plus plus — bộ nhớ lai có thể xác minh cho agent tự động. Dự án Sui Overflow, track Walrus. Nhanh ở local, bền vững trên Walrus, kinh tế trên Sui.
Agents forget between sessions. Opaque databases can't prove what was remembered. Marketplaces need portable memory — not screenshots. And inference can't wait on the network every token.
Agent quên giữa các phiên làm việc. Cơ sở dữ liệu mờ không chứng minh được agent nhớ gì. Thị trường memory cần dữ liệu mang đi được — không phải ảnh chụp màn hình.
MemWal plus plus is three layers: SQLite local-first, MemWal to Walrus for durable blobs, and Sui Move for packs, marketplace, and WAL bounties. Redact and score before anything leaves the machine.
Ba lớp: SQLite local-first, MemWal đẩy lên Walrus, Sui Move cho pack, marketplace và bounty WAL. Lọc PII và chấm điểm chất lượng trước khi upload.
The path is explicit: local store, redaction, quality gate, then remember to Walrus. Every promoted row gets a walrus blob id — the same id Sui bounties reference on fulfillment.
Luồng rõ ràng: local store, redact, quality gate, rồi remember lên Walrus. Mỗi dòng được promote có blob id — cùng id mà bounty Sui dùng khi fulfill.
Demo one: clone the repo, pnpm install, pnpm agent demo. No API keys. You'll see beforeRemember, afterThink, and onTaskComplete — exit code zero proves the architecture.
Demo một: clone repo, cài đặt, chạy agent demo. Không cần API key. Thấy đủ vòng đời hook — exit code zero là đủ chứng minh kiến trúc.
Demo two: bounty hunt — poster and hunter agents on the same sync service. Offline proves coordination. With MemWal env vars, watch a real blob id land on mainnet-ready fulfillment.
Demo hai: bounty hunt — agent poster và hunter cùng sync service. Offline chứng minh phối hợp đa agent. Bật MemWal env thì thấy blob id thật trên luồng fulfill.
Live dashboard at memwalpp dash dashboard dot vercel dot app. Walrus-grade UI, wallet connect, judge commands, and kiosk chain actions on mainnet.
Dashboard live trên Vercel. Giao diện Walrus, kết nối ví, lệnh cho judge, và kiosk chain actions trên mainnet.
Built for Walrus: durable blobs, verifiable blob ids, programmable access through Move, and privacy enforced before upload. Not wallpaper — it's the product story.
Làm cho Walrus: blob bền, id xác minh được, truy cập lập trình qua Move, riêng tư trước khi upload. Đây là cốt lõy sản phẩm.
End to end in code: hooks to blob id to Move fulfillment. Runnable in three minutes without keys. Move v2 bootstrapped on mainnet. MCP server and dashboard wallet PTBs — all in one monorepo.
End-to-end trong code: hook → blob id → fulfill Move. Chạy được trong ba phút không cần key. Move v2 đã bootstrap mainnet. MCP server và dashboard — một monorepo.
Try it now — star the repo, open the live demo, run both agent CLIs. Judge guide in the repo root. MemWal plus plus. Thanks for watching.
Thử ngay — star repo, mở demo live, chạy hai CLI agent. Judge guide ở thư mục gốc. Cảm ơn đã xem MemWal plus plus.